brastop.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy and Security - Brastop

Mid-Season SALE ♥ Up to 70% OFF - Ends Sunday __

  * At Brastop we take the privacy of all our customers very seriously and we are 100% committed to protecting all personal information that we hold.  The following privacy policy explains in detail the types of information we collect, how we may use it and the procedures we have in place to make sure that it is kept safe and secure.

  * Your Personal Information
  * When you visit Brastop we collect personal information about you depending on how you interact with the website, sign up for an account or our email marketing, contact us with an enquiry or complaint and whether or not you make a purchase with us. The types of information we may collect include:

Name, email address, postal address, telephone number, date of birth, bra size, whether you are male or female, purchase information such as credit card details and product preferences

We use this information to process and fulfil your order. Information of this nature will only ever be used for marketing purposes if you have previously given us your consent to do so.

  * Website Information Collected
  * When you visit the Brastop website we collect some information related to your visit.  This information includes your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, device type and other related information if you choose to share it with us such as location data and how you use our website (eg; average time on the site). We use this information to monitor and improve our website so that we can give you the best possible shopping experience.  We also use cookies to collect information about the pages you visit. For further information about cookies and how we use them please see our Cookie Policy.

  * Marketing
  * If you have previously given us consent to do so, from time to time we will send you marketing messages by email, SMS or post in order to keep you up to date on all the latest offers, promotions, sales and latest arrivals at Brastop.

You can of course opt out of all marketing communications at any point should you wish to do so. All of our email marketing messages include an unsubscribe option which is clearly marked. If you have a registered account with us, you can also unsubscribe in your account registration page here: <https://www.brastop.com/customer/info>

Or you can also contact our customer services team and request to unsubscribe. Customer services can be contacted here. Once you have unsubscribed from marketing communications you will no longer receive any further marketing messages from us. If contacting us via email or phone with an unsubscribe request, please be aware that it may take a few days for the request to be processed depending on how busy we are. You may therefore receive a marketing message from us whilst your request is being processed.

If you have opted out of receiving marketing messages, you will still receive notifications from us regarding service. This will include order and delivery updates or any communications around the status of your order.

  * Cookies and Online Advertising
  * In line with most other online companies, we use technology called ‘cookies’ on our website.  Cookies are small text files that are stored by your browser on your PC, phone or tablet when you visit Brastop.com. They are used to record how you interact with the website when you visit.  They do not store or contain any personal or confidential information such as address or name.

Cookies are an essential tool for us to provide you with the best possible website experience.  Some cookies are required for you to navigate and use site functions like Add to Bad or Add to Wishlist. Other cookies help us improve the website by recording how you interact with the pages and some cookies are used to deliver relevant adverts to you. By using our website, you consent to the use of cookies on your device.

If you want to delete any cookies on your computer or device, the ‘Help’ section in your browser will provide instructions on how to do so. Please note that if you do choose to delete cookies, your website experience may be affected and you  may not be able to use certain functions on the website.

At Brastop we undertake online advertising to keep our customers and visitors aware of the latest promotions and sales and to help you see and find our products.

For online advertising, we use third-party advertising service vendors to serve targeted Brastop banners and ads which may be shown to you when you are visiting other websites or apps. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, pixels, ad tags and mobile identifiers to serve relevant ads.  The banners and ads that you may see will be based on information we hold about you or your previous use of Brastop.com (items searched for on the website or product pages browsed) or on Brastop banners and ads that you previously interacted with.

  * Security and Fraud Prevention
  * We would like to reassure you that all online transactions are completely secure because all credit and debit card details that you send o us are encrypted and sent across a secure connection.

There will be a security icon in the bottom right hand corner of your browser to signify you are in secure mode - this is usually depicted as either a padlock or key symbol. Another check is that during payment, the address at the top of the browser will begin https:// rather than https://.

The website is tested and certified daily to pass the McAfee Secure Security Scan. To help address concerns about possible hacker access to your confidential data, and the safety of visiting this site, the "live" McAfee Secure mark appears only when this site passes the daily McAfee Secure tests.

Where a password is required to access certain areas of our website including logging on to your account, you are responsible for keeping your password secure and confidential. Please do not share or disclose your password with any other person.

In order to protect against the fraudulent use of credit cards, we may carry our security checks on orders. This may require us to contact you by telephone before your order is processed and dispatched.  We may require you to confirm information provided on your order such as billing name and address and card issuer details.  This is required sometimes as a necessary precaution in the interests of fraud prevention. If you have any concerns about this or regarding security in general, please contact our customer services team here.

  * Retention of Personal Information
  * We only keep your personal information as long as necessary for the purposes we collected it, or as otherwise required by law.

You have the right to be informed about any personal information we hold on you and how it is being used. You also have the right to access the personal information we hold about you and to request the correction of incorrect personal information in your account.

You have the right to request that we delete any data we hold on you.

You have the right to stop receiving any marketing messages from us and this an be done by logging into your account, unsubscribing from email messages or you can send a request to our customer services team here.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, make a complaint or have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please customer services team here.

  * Sharing Your Information
  * We do not and would never sell any of your personal information to any third party. This includes personal information we hold on you such as name, address, email address or credit card information. Your trust is incredibly important to us and as a trusted retailer this is a top priority for us.

We collect website information such as site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we pass on to third parties in order for us to improve the website experience for customers. Any information of this nature that we pass on to third parties is done so on an aggregated and anonymous basis and we make sure that it does not contain anything that can identify customers.

  * Changes to our Privacy Policy
  * We keep our Privacy Policy under review at all times. We may therefore periodically update this Privacy Policy to reflect any new regulatory requirements and changes in how we collect or use information. Any changes made will be posted on this page. We therefore recommend returning here regularly to view our most up to date privacy notice.

  * Contacting Us
  * If for any reason you need to contact us about any elements on this page or for any general enquiries please do not hesitate to get in touch. We are happy to respond to any questions or concerns you may have about your privacy or the data we hold on you.

Should you wish to do so, you can contact our customer services team here or you can write to us at the address below.

Brastop Customer Services  
Brastop Ltd  
Unit 1 Hawthorn Centre  
Elmgrove Road  
Harrow  
HA1 2RF

Get Exclusive Offers

Our emails are filled with the latest discounts, special offers, new product and body positive news.

By clicking SIGN UP you are accepting our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy. You can unsubscribe at any time.

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience. If you continue, we assume that you consent to receive all cookies. Learn More
